var questionArray = [{

    question: 'American politician and diplomat Madeleine Albright was born in what central European country?',
    choices: ['Germany','Poland','Serbia','Czechoslovakia',],
    answer: 'Czechoslovakia',
},
{
    question: 'At the time of his assassination, what play was Abraham Lincoln watching?]',
    choices: ['Carmen',	'Our American Cousin','Uncle Vanya','Mary Stuart',],
    answer: 'Our American Cousin',
},
{  
    question: 'Where was Richard Nixon when he delivered his infamous “I am not a crook” speech?',
    choices: ['Portland, Oregon	Washington', 'D.C.','Orlando, Florida',	'New York, New York'],
    answer: 'Orlando,florida',
},
{
    question: 'In 1952, Albert Einstein was offered the presidency of which country?',
    choices: ['Israel',	'Germany','England','America'],
    answer: 'Israel',
},
{
    question: 'Who was first U.S. president to be impeached?',
    choices:[ 'Andrew Johnson',	'Donald Trump',	'Richard Nixon','Bill Clinton',],
    answer: 'Andrew Johnson',
},
{
    question: 'Who became both a vice president and president of the United States without ever being elected to either office?',
    choices:['James Madison',	'Gerald Ford',	'Zachary Taylor',	'Dwight D. Eisenhower'],
    answer: 'Gerald Ford',
},
{
    question: 'Who was the first female Prime Minister of a European country?',
    choices: ['Angela Merkel', 	'Margaret Thatcher', 	'Indira Gandhi',	'Milka Planinc'],
    answer: 'Margaret Thatcher',
},
{
    question: 'Which U.S. president issued the Emancipation Proclamation?',
    choices: ['James Buchanan',	'Andrew Johnson',	'Abraham Lincon',	'Theodore Roosevelt'],
    answer: 'Abraham Lincon',
},
{
    question: 'The Bill of Rights contains how many of the first amendments to the United States Constitution?',
    choices: ['Eight',	'Nine',	'Ten',	'Eleven',],
    answer: 'Ten',
},
{
    question: 'Who was the first U.S. president that was born a citizen of the United States?',
    choices: ['George Washington',	'John Adams',	'Thomas Jefferson',	'Martin Van Buren',],
    answer: 'Matin Van Buren',
}

];






